https://shop.wildrepublic.com/pages/privacy-policy

Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Introduction
At Wild Republic, we strive to maintain a safe and secure online space for you to shop and for your children to play. The following section addresses any privacy concerns that you might have regarding you or your child’s navigation of our online site. Wild Republic will not collect any personal information about individuals except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. Examples of such information are: name, postal address, email address, phone number, birthday and product commentary. We currently do not collect any information from anyone browsing the site or using the interactive games and activities. This includes games, animated content and e-Postcards. The only time we will ask for your information is when you are making a purchase or when you review a product.
Making a Purchase
When you make a purchase on our site, your transaction will be conducted through a secure server that protects your credit card and personal information including but not limited to: your name, address, billing address, credit card and expiration date, e-mail and telephone number. This information will not be stored or sold to any third party. When you purchase products from Wild Republic or register for any Wild Republic services, we may automatically place you on our list to receive email regarding updates about special offers, new products, and new services. If you do not wish to receive email updates, please send an e-mail to humans@wildrepublic.com and type "REMOVE" in the subject line.
Reviewing a Product
You will have the option to review our products after you make a purchase and if you chose to do so, we will ask for your name and a legitimate e-mail address in order to filter out spam messages. Your e-mail will not be published on our site.
Customer Information
Currently, Wild Republic does not sell, rent, or loan any identifiable information regarding its customers to any third party. Any information you give us is held with the utmost care and security, and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Wild Republic If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Cookies
Wild Republic uses a feature of your Internet web browser called a cookie to assign a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are files that your web browser places on your computer's hard drive. Wild Republic creates and then uses these cookie files to track your clicks as you go through the Wild Republic Site. Wild Republic only uses cookies to (1) keep track of items you put into your shopping cart, (2) to tell us whether you have visited Wild Republic International previously, and (3) to help us determine whether you came to Wild Republic International from a particular Internet link or banner advertisement. Cookies can also be used to help save and retrieve passwords used on the Wild Republic International Site and information on past purchases and other preferences, saving you from having to re-enter this information upon every visit to the Wild Republic Site. Cookies cannot be used by Wild Republic to retrieve any personal information about you unless you have previously purchased from or registered with Wild Republic. Wild Republic does not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer unless such information was knowingly and willingly provided by you.
International Users
This website can be accessed from countries around the world and may contain references to Services that are not available in your country. These references do not imply that Wild Republic intends to offer such Services in your country. The site is controlled, operated and administered by offices within the United States of America. Wild Republic makes no representation that the website and its Services are appropriate or available for use at other locations outside the United States, and access to this website from territories where the website and Services are illegal is prohibited. If you access the website from a location outside the United States, you are responsible for compliance with all local laws.
Contacting Us
Wild Republic strongly supports practicing online safety and welcomes suggestions or questions regarding our policies.
Wild Republic 1955 Midway Drive Twinsburg, Ohio 44087 Tel: 330-425-2550 Fax: 330-425-3777 Toll Free: 1-800-800-9678
FAQs
Cleaning Your Wild Republic Stuffed Animals
Online policies
Contact us
Just added to your wishlist:
[[BODY]]
[[TIMER_FOOTER]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON1_LABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON2_LABEL]]
×
[[HEADER]]
[[MINIMIZED]]
[[BODY]]
[[FOOTER]]
[[TIMER_FOOTER]]
Powered By Discount Ninja
[[TEXT]]
×
Powered By Discount Ninja
[[HEADER]]
[[BODY]]
[[FOOTER]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON1LABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON2LABEL]]
[[NOTHANKSBUTTONLABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON1LABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON2LABEL]]
[[NOTHANKSBUTTONLABEL]]
[[TEXT]]
[[HEADER]]
Powered By Discount Ninja
[[BODY]]
[[QUANTITY_LABEL]]
[[PRICE_LABEL]]
[[TIER_ROW]]
[[PRICE]]
[[LABEL]]
[[HEADER]]
[[BODY]]
[[FOOTER]]
[[ROW]]
WHAT'S YOUR EMAIL?
ADD TO WISHLIST
Product has been added to your wishlist.
You can view your wishlist by creating or login account.
